I want to kindly request if you could be
upstanding for the reading of God's
word.
Uh, please turn with me to the book of
Isaiah chapter 60.
Isaiah
the prophet
chapter 60 from verse 1.
Isaiah 60
Screens are really slow here.
Whoever is in the screens, please wake
up.
We are in church.
60 from verse 1, not 16.
The Bible says, "Arise, shine, for your
light has come
and the glory of the Lord is risen upon
you.
For behold, the darkness shall cover the
earth
and deep darkness the people.
But the Lord will arise over you
and his glory will be seen upon you.
The Gentiles shall come to your light
and kings to the brightness of your
rising.
Lift up your eyes all around and see.
They all gather together.
They come to you.
Your sons shall come from afar.
And your daughters shall be nursed at
your side.
Then
you shall see and become radiant.
And your heart shall swell with joy.
Because the abundance of the sea
shall be turned to you.
The wealth of the Gentiles
shall come to you.
The multitudes of the camels
shall cover your land.
The dromedaries of Midian, Ephah,
all those from Sheba shall come.
They shall bring gold
and incense.
And they shall proclaim
the praises
of the Lord.
Father, bless the reading of your word
to our hearts this morning. Let your
name be glorified.
The church be edified.
And hell be terrified.
Thank you for the anointing that makes
this work easy.
Let shackles be broken.
Yokes be destroyed.
Your name be glorified.
We thank you. We bless you in Jesus'
name. Somebody shout amen.
And amen. You may be seated in the
presence of the Lord.
Allow me for the few minutes I'm before
you this morning to speak on the subject
of entitled the power
of a divine shift.
The power
Isaiah chapter 60
sits in the final section of Isaiah,
which is Isaiah chapter 55 to Isaiah
10 chapters
which are called the third
Isaiah.
Brothers and sisters, ladies and
gentlemen, this is the portion of
scripture
that speaks of God's people after exile.
They have been in exile in Babylon and
now
have been delivered
under the mighty kingdom of the Persians
back to Jerusalem.
They are discouraged,
struggling
and far from the glorious restoration
they expected.
They are going through the motions.
And even the deliverance they
experienced
was not as exciting as they thought
because
the struggles are real.
Very far from the glorious restoration
that had been promised in scripture.
God from heaven above
had to interrupt their daily living.
Church,
a shift
is when God interrupts your normal
to introduce
your next level.
There cannot really be a shift without
God interrupting your normal,
your usual,
what you're used to.
You can't talk about a shift
without a divine
interruption.
You see, when God steps into your
normal,
ordinary,
struggles,
discouragements,
challenges,
God brings
seasons.
Doors open
and patterns break.
Yes.
Destinies are accelerated when God
steps into the picture.
It's my prayer this morning, even as we
kick off this shift conference,
that God in the heaven
will step into your situation
and change from bads
to best.
I pray that this morning that God will
interrupt your situation from the normal
mundane.
Uh from the normal usual that you're
used to
and bring in
another season for his glory.
Somebody say amen.
Ladies and gentlemen, brothers and
sisters,
normally for you to have a shift, people
really have to work a lot.
Have to really struggle
to bring in a shift.
But the divine shift that I'm talking
about this morning is basically
God's shift that one that when God
comes, it just takes
a move
and everything changes.
It's important to note
that
divine shifts
are initiated
by God.
Ezequiel chapter 21 and verse 27 says,
"I will overturn, overturn,
overturn it."
That sounds like a word for somebody
this morning.
Uh I repeat, Ezequiel 21 and verse 27
says, "I will overturn, overturn,
overturn it." There's some stuff that
needs to be overturned even as we kick
off
this shift conference.
Uh I need to hear somebody say, "Amen."
The shifts are not man-made, they're
God-ordained.
Uh you don't force it.
Uh you only have to position your share
self for the shift uh that God is
bringing your way.
Uh somebody has to be in the [snorts]
right position just so things to happen.
I was doing something recently about uh
the power of just presence. And when I
was talking about the power of presence
uh
uh I can also think about the the power
of positioning.
Being in the right position means a lot
uh
in the kingdom of God. Uh just being at
the right time, the right place.
Destinies have been known to change
because somebody was in the right place
at the right time. I feel like somebody
today is in the right place at the right
time even as we kick off this shift
seems uh come on. Touch your neighbor
and tell them you look like you're the
one he's talking about.
When God decides
when God initiates
systems bow
protocols change
and favor speaks.
Ah, yes. I want to feel like I'm
preaching in a church that is in the
spirit that I am this morning.
When God speaks, it interrupts
systems bow and the protocols change
and favor speaks.
Yes?
Uh, shifts
initiated
by God.
But you see, it's not just the shifts
are initiated by God.
When shifts happen
they break patterns.
The Bible says in the book of Isaiah 43
and verse 19 behold, I will do a new
thing.
Every divine shift disrupts disrupts
rather
cycles
generational delays
uh, near success syndromes
and repeated disappointments.
Uh, shifts come to break generational
curses.
Uh, shift comes to pull you out of the
rut. Shifts come to pull you out of
getting stuck. Uh, shifts come to get
you out of going
in cycles.
If you've been going in cycles
and you've been going through just the
normal and you've never experienced the
extraordinary
uh, the Bible tells us that God is about
to do a new thing. And when God does a
new thing
he interrupts
generational delays, things that have
kept your generations, your grandfather
who struggled through the same thing,
your father struggled through the same
thing. WHEN A SHIFT HAPPENS,
God in heaven interrupts that
generational delay and he brings about
success and breakthroughs that cannot be
humanly explained.
You see, you cannot really carry old
patterns to this shift that we are
talking about. The old has to give way
to the new.
SO, GOD SAYS, "Forgetting the things of
the past,
behold,
I do a new thing." It's It's A BEHOLDING
YOU HAVE TO DO. Look at your neighbor
this morning and tell them, "You have to
behold that he is doing a new thing."
Come on. Come on. Come on. You have to
behold that he is doing a new thing.
It's Oh my God. One of the saddest thing
is for God to be doing a new thing and
you're not even aware about it.
You're not even aware about it.
How blind can somebody be for God in
heaven to come and to interrupt a
generational system that has plagued
people for years and you're not even
aware about the new thing that God is
doing. So, God comes as a behold, "Open
your spiritual eyes and see that God is
doing a new thing even as we enter into
the shift that God has chosen to
initiate."
What used to stop you, what used to be a
block for you,
God says it will not stop you anymore
because there's a new shift. I don't
know if you're excited like I am, but
look your neighbor and tell them it will
not stop you again.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, it will not stop
you again. Your history, your past, the
things that kept you in the back, the
things that were a hindrance, the Bible
says that they will not stop you again
because there's a new shift. I pray and
I trust that you will not miss any
season of this new season that God is
ushering us into. I FEEL LIKE GOD IS
JUST GOING TO CARRY US THROUGH THIS NEW
SHIFT AND THAT YOU WILL NOT BE ANYWHERE
else but just be in the presence
of God.
Shifts.
Shifts often come through pressure.
Uh the Bible says in the book of 2
Corinthians chapter 4 and verse 8,
"We are troubled on every side, yet not
distressed."
For you see, pressure
is not punishment.
Pressure
is preparation.
And some of you have BEEN THROUGH SO
MUCH PRESSURE.
It has been really tough.
It has been rough.
And you even wondered if God was still
with you.
I came to remind you this morning that
pressure
is not punishment but preparation.
At
normally just before God brings A SHIFT,
HE CAUSES you to go through some
preparation in the name of pressure.
Just before God brings this new thing
that he's about to bring into your life,
he causes you to go through stuff
to prepare you for the next level.
Uh Paul says that Uh, are troubled on
every side, yet not distressed.
So, what feels like breaking is often
a birthing.
Even a seed
must
break
before it grows.
AND BEFORE God brings this shift,
SOME OF YOU HAVE GONE THROUGH A lot of
hell and high water.
Some of you have gone through tough
preparatory stages and forms and uh
places that you've been through, things
that have happened to you, uh things
that have been said to you, and on and
on. Normally, before the seed grows,
it has to break.
Yes.
Shift.
A shift that comes from God
comes through pressure.
Shifts change
your identity.
AND THAT WHEN GOD
BEGINS THE SHIFT,
HE WILL CHANGE YOUR IDENTITY.
GOD HAD TO change Jacob
to become Israel
before THE MAJOR SHIFT.
GOD had to change Abram
to Abraham
BEFORE THE MAJOR SHIFT.
FOR YOU SEE, YOUR IDENTITY SHIFTS before
your environment does.
Uh, you didn't get that.
YOUR IDENTITY SHIFTS
BEFORE YOUR ENVIRONMENT DOES.
If your environment changes and your
identity has not been changed by God,
there'll be nothing much. You normally
say, you know, a lizard in Kenya is a
lizard in the US. There's no way you can
be a crocodile because you moved to the
US. Come on, somebody.
BUT IF GOD CHANGES YOUR IDENTITY
AND SHIFTS IT TO ANOTHER LEVEL,
IT DOESN'T MATTER YOUR
FOR WHERE [screaming] YOU GO, YOU'RE
GOING TO BE BLESSED IF YOUR identity is
blessed.
If they take you to Mathare, you're
going to be blessed. If they take you to
Mandera Mandera, you're going to be
blessed. Wherever they take you, you're
going to be blessed because IT'S YOUR
IDENTITY. SOME OF YOU HAVE GOT A DNA OF
BLESSING THAT WHEREVER they post you
I've had so many people wondering about
being changed from one location to
another. But let me tell you, JOSEPH WAS
IN EGYPT AND THE BIBLE SAYS EGYPT WAS
BLESSED BECAUSE JOSEPH WAS AROUND. YOUR
IDENTITY CHANGES WHEN THE SHIFT TAKES
PLACE. AH, [screaming] LOOK AT SOMEONE
AND TELL THEM, "I AM BLESSED."
I AM BLESSED. WHEREVER THEY TAKE YOU,
whatever they do, WHATEVER THE POSITION
THEY GIVE YOU, IT DOES NOT MATTER. A
BLESSED INDIVIDUAL IS A BLESSED
INDIVIDUAL. AH, IN KENYA, IN ITALY,
WHEREVER THEY ARE, EVEN IN SOMALIA, YOU
WILL STILL BE BLESSED BECAUSE GOD, ONCE
HE HAS CHANGED YOUR SHIFT, IT'S NOT YOUR
GEOGRAPHY.
AH, ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME THIS
MORNING?
IT'S NOT YOUR GEOGRAPHY THAT MATTERS.
YOUR GEOGRAPHY WILL CHANGE BECAUSE OF
YOU, BUT NOT VICE VERSA.
HALLELUJAH.
GLORY TO GOD. A SHIFT COMES TO CHANGE
YOUR NAME. Read your Bible, you'll see
that people that God brought a shift
into their lives. The first thing he did
is to change their identity. And I feel
LIKE IN THIS SHIFT CONFERENCE, YOUR NAME
IS GOING TO CHANGE.
OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH. THEY CALLED YOU POOR,
THEY'RE GOING TO CHANGE THAT NAME. THEY
CALLED YOU SICK, THEY'RE GOING TO CHANGE
THAT NAME. THEY CALLED YOU BROKE,
THEY'RE GOING TO CHANGE THAT NAME. AM I
TALKING TO SOMEBODY THIS MORNING?
WHATEVER NAME THEY CALLED YOU THAT WAS
NEGATIVE, THEY'RE GOING TO CHANGE IT.
OH, YES, JABEZ'S IDENTITY HAD TO BE
CHANGED. AND WHEN HE CHANGED HIS
IDENTITY, HIS GEOGRAPHY BEGAN TO CHANGE.
LOOK AT SOMEBODY AND TELL THEM I AM
BLESSED.
OH, WHO IS IT THAT I CAME TO PREACH TO
THIS MORNING? I AM BLESSED. I AM
BLESSED. IT'S NOT YOUR FATHER, IT'S NOT
YOUR MOTHER, IT'S NOT YOUR TRIBE. ALL
HAS TO DO WITH A SHIFT THAT GOD IS
BRINGING INTO YOUR LIFE DURING THIS
WEEK. GOD IS GOING TO CHANGE YOUR
DESTINY. GOD,
>> [screaming]
>> AM I TALKING TO YOU?
IDENTITY CHANGES.
GOD [screaming] BEGINS TO CHANGE YOUR
IDENTITY.
Glory to God.
Hallelujah.
Because you're blessed.
YOU'LL GO TO PLACES AND YOU'LL BE
SITTING AT THE BACK AND THEY'LL BE
TELLING YOU, "NO, you don't belong
there. You belong to the front."
Are you listening? Am I talking to you
this morning? Your identity has changed.
WHEN YOUR IDENTITY CHANGES, YOU CANNOT
BE HIDDEN. WHEN YOUR IDENTITY CHANGES,
THEY WILL RECOGNIZE YOU. WHEN YOUR
IDENTITY OH, CHURCH, COME ON. COME ON.
COME ON. COME ON. COME ON. YOUR IDENTITY
IS CHANGING. STAND UP ON YOUR FEET AND
TOUCH THE THREE PEOPLE AND TELL THEM MY
IDENTITY IS CHANGING.
OH, COME ON. MY IDENTITY IS CHANGING. I
FEEL LIKE I'M TALKING TO SOMEBODY TODAY.
MY IDENTITY IS CHANGING. OH, YEAH, YEAH,
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, [screaming] YEAH. MY
IDENTITY AND IT ALL CHANGES BECAUSE OF A
SHIFT.
>> MAY GOD CHANGE YOUR IDENTITY THIS WEEK.
I SAID, MAY GOD CHANGE YOUR IDENTITY
THIS WEEK.
MAY CALLS BEGIN TO FLOW ON YOUR PHONE
AND GOOD CALLS FOR THAT MATTER IN JESUS
NAME. AM I TALKING TO SOMEBODY? MAY GOOD
EMAILS BEGIN TO TRACE YOU AND TO FOLLOW
YOU IN THE MIGHTY NAME OF JESUS BECAUSE
YOU ARE GETTING INTO A SHIFT. THINGS ARE
CHANGING. IT'S NOT GOING TO BE NORMAL
ANYMORE.
>> [screaming]
>> I HAVE EXPERIENCED
A SHIFT.
SIT DOWN, LET ME TALK TO YOU.
WHEN A SHIFT HAPPENS,
YOUR IDENTITY CHANGES.
PEOPLE WILL come looking for you
and you'll begin TO WONDER WHAT
HAPPENED. BUT IT'S GOT NOTHING TO DO
WITH YOU. IT'S GOT EVERYTHING TO DO WITH
JEHOVAH GOD AND THAT'S WHY WE SAY, "TO
GOD BE THE GLORY FOR THE GREAT THINGS HE
HAS DONE." AH, THIS MORNING WE WERE
SINGING that great hymn, "HE HAS DONE
GREAT THINGS." AND LET ME TELL YOU, AS
HE BEGAN to sing that song, YOU COULD
ALL GO THROUGH THE CATALOG OF THE GREAT
THINGS THAT GOD HAS DONE INTO YOUR LIFE.
HE SAVED YOU. HE PURCHASED YOU WITH HIS
PRECIOUS BLOOD. HE MADE A WAY WHERE
THERE WAS NO WAY. HE PROVIDED FOR YOU
WHEN YOU DIDN'T EVEN KNOW WHERE THE
MONEY IS COMING FROM. HE OPENED DOORS
WHEN YOU DIDN'T SEE HOW THEY WERE GOING
TO BE OPENED AND HE HAS DONE GREAT
THINGS. YOUR IDENTITY THIS WEEK IS ABOUT
TO CHANGE.
YOUR IDENTITY [screaming] OH, COME ON,
SOMEBODY.
YOUR IDENTITY
IS about to change.
There's a shift.
I'm reminded of the four lepers. The
other thing I had the other the other
point I had was the shift comes as a
result of obedience.
THE LEPERS WHO WERE cleansed
were not cleansed when they were
stationary.
They were told to go and show themselves
to the priests.
The Bible says as they went in obedience
TO SHOW THEMSELVES
TO THE PRIESTS. AS THEY OBEYED GOD, AS
THEY WERE IN MOTION, CHANGES BEGAN TO
HAPPEN.
YOUR SHIFT HAPPENS AS YOU BEGIN to walk
in obedience to the will OF GOD.
BROTHERS AND SISTERS, ladies and
gentlemen, THIS WEEK IS THE SHIFT WEEK.
WE ARE WALKING TOWARDS THE PROMISES OF
GOD. WE ARE WALKING TOWARDS THE WILL OF
GOD. AM I TALKING TO YOU THIS MORNING?
WE ARE WALKING TOWARDS THE ORDINANCES OF
JEHOVAH GOD. AS THE LEPERS BEGAN to
walk, they began to be cleansed. YOU
HAVE BEGUN YOUR CLEANSING THIS MORNING
IN THIS SERVICE. THINGS ARE BEGINNING TO
FALL. THINGS ARE BEGINNING TO FALL.
CHAINS ARE FALLING OFF. AM I TALKING TO
YOU? SOMEBODY WHO I'M TALKING TO, CAN
YOU SHOUT AMEN? [screaming]
CHAINS ARE FALLING. BONDAGES ARE GOING
OUT. THIS IS THE WEEK OF THE SHIFT.
[screaming] I FEEL GOD IS DOING
SOMETHING. THE PRESENCE OF THE LORD IS
IN THE HOUSE. DEVILS HAVE TO GO. WITCHES
HAVE TO BE DEFEATED. ARE YOU LISTENING
TO WHAT I AM SAYING?
OH, YEAH.
SHIFTS.
WHEN THE SHIFT HAPPENS,
LIFE HAS TO BE DISRUPTED.
IT CANNOT [screaming] BE NORMAL.
YOUR THINKING BEGINS TO CHANGE.
THE WAY YOU REASON BEGINS TO CHANGE.
THERE'S A TRANSFORMATION THAT TAKES
PLACE
BECAUSE A SHIFT HAS TAKEN PLACE. IT
CANNOT JUST BE THE SAME JANUARY,
FEBRUARY, MARCH TO DECEMBER.
SHIFTS COME to disrupt
the normal.
And the shift happens
like we read in the book of Acts chapter
16 and verse 25.
IT HAPPENS SUDDENLY.
BIBLE SAYS AT midnight Paul and Silas
prayed.
For midnight represents the lowest
point,
the darkest moment.
But when shifts come,
even in your lowest point,
even in the darkest time,
the Bible says when the shift happened,
chains began to break.
Doors were opened.
Systems
collapsed.
YOUR SUDDENLY
is tied
to your consistency
in God.
A lot of you have been consistent with
God
and have been wondering what is
happening.
A lot of you have been faithful with God
thinking that God has forgotten you.
But this week we come to remind you that
the shift is TAKING PLACE.
UH CHANGE IS TAKING PLACE.
Uh you don't look like people who really
want the shift that I'm talking about.
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE SHIFT IS HAPPENING
THIS WEEK. MY LIFE IS CHANGING THIS
WEEK. YOUR AMEN IS SO ANEMIC. I WANT TO
TELL YOU YOUR SHIFT IS TAKING PLACE.
UH CHURCH, CAN YOU HEAR WHAT I AM
TALKING ABOUT? THIS WEEK I'M NOT COMING
OUT THE SAME WAY. THIS WEEK I'M NOT
COMING OUT THE SAME ORDINARY PERSON. GOD
[screaming]
IS VISITING MY SITUATION. GOD IS
CHANGING AND INTERRUPTING
WHAT WAS BUGGING ME. THE DOORS THAT WERE
CLOSED, HE'S MAKING A WAY THERE WHERE
THERE WAS NO WAY. LOOK AT YOUR NEIGHBOR
AND GIVE THEM A HIGH FIVE AND TELL THEM
HE'S TALKING ABOUT ME.
SHIFT CONFERENCE.
What a powerful theme
for this week.
Yes.
Shifts
require courage.
Arise.
Go over
this Jordan.
Joshua chapter 1 and verse 2.
FOR YOU SEE, CROSSING OVER
demands boldness.
Fear will try to keep you in your
familiar.
Faith
will push you into the promise.
YOU CANNOT SHIFT and stay comfortable
at the same time.
THE CHILDREN OF ISRAEL,
FOR THEM TO EXPERIENCE THE SHIFT that
God had for them,
HAD TO GET TO THAT PLACE
WHERE THEY HAD TO STEP INTO THE JORDAN.
AS SCARY AS IT WAS,
AS FEARFUL AS IT WAS,
THEY HAD TO STEP INTO THE JORDAN RIVER.
AND GOD TOLD THEM, "THE MOMENT YOUR FEET
STEP INTO THE JORDAN RIVER,
THE WATERS WILL STOP."
THIS IS THE WEEK. OH, Lord Jesus.
OH, [screaming] LORD JESUS,
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL SAY,
"I HAVE HEARD THE WORD OF THE LORD AND I
AM STEPPING INTO MY JORDAN.
YOU WILL STEP INTO THE JORDAN BY FAITH
BECAUSE YOU HAVE LIVED IN FEAR FOR TOO
LONG. THE FEAR HAS KEPT YOU A PRISONER
ALL YOUR LIFE. BUT AS THE SHIFT OF GOD
BEGINS TO HAPPEN, SOMEBODY IS GOING TO
STEP INTO THAT JORDAN AND THE WATERS ARE
GOING TO PART.
CAN YOU SAY HALLELUJAH TO JESUS?
I DON'T KNOW WHO I came TO PREACH TO,
BUT I SEE THE JORDAN PARTING. I SEE THE
RIVER GIVING WAY. I SEE THE RIVER GOING
ASIDE.
OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>> [clears throat]
>> SOMEBODY IN THIS PLACE
IS GETTING INTO THEIR JORDAN EXPERIENCE
THIS WEEK.
OH, STAND UP ON YOUR FEET AND GIVE
SOMEBODY A HIGH FIVE AND TELL THEM IT'S
ME.
IT'S ME. IT'S ME. IT'S ME. IT'S ME. IT'S
ME. THE SHIFT IS TAKING PLACE. IT IS ME
HE'S TALKING ABOUT. OH, YEAH. IT IS ME.
IT IS ME HE'S TALKING ABOUT. THE JORDAN
HAS TO PART. YOU HAVE BEEN KEPT TOO LONG
IN THE SAME POSITION. IT IS TIME TO STEP
INTO THE JORDAN.
IT IS TIME TO STEP INTO YOUR JORDAN.
[screaming]
SHIFT.
HALLELUJAH.
THE SHIFT.
THE SHIFT IS TAKING PLACE.
THE SHIFT IN YOUR PLACE OF WORK IS
TAKING PLACE. THE SHIFT IN YOUR HOME IS
TAKING PLACE. THE SHIFT IN YOUR CAREER
IS TAKING PLACE. THE SHIFT IN YOUR
BUSINESS IS TAKING PLACE. THE SHIFT IS
TAKING PLACE IN YOUR RELATIONSHIP. OH,
COME ON, COME ON, COME ON, COME ON. THE
SHIFT IS TAKING PLACE. WHO IS IT THAT I
TOLD THE SHIFT IS TAKING PLACE.
KING OF GLORY.
KING OF GLORY,
KING OF GLORY, THIS SHIFT IS HAPPENING.
GOD, HAVE YOUR WAY.
HAVE YOUR [screaming] WAY.
STEPPED INTO IT.
THE JORDAN.
It takes courage.
It takes fortitude. It takes faith. IT
TAKES YOU WALKING WITH GOD. IT TAKES YOU
SAYING, "GOD, IT'S ME. IT'S ME. IT'S ME.
I AM STEPPING INTO MY JORDAN." SOMEBODY
THIS WEEK IS NOT GOING TO BE PASSED BY.
SOMEBODY THIS WEEK IS GOING TO STEP INTO
THEIR JORDAN AND THE WATERS WILL GO
BACK. SOMEBODY SAY, [screaming]
"HALLELUJAH."
AS THEY stepped into the water,
the waters
rolled
back
and the shift
they always dreamed of,
of getting into the promised land,
took place.
You are where you are today
because you've not had the faith
to step into your Jordan for the shift
to take place. Let me say something.
You have been waiting on God
and God is waiting on you.
I want to repeat.
You have been waiting on God
and God
is waiting
on you
to step
into
your Jordan.
This
is your week
of change.
>> [music]
>> This
is your week
of change.
I want to make some prophetic
declarations.
Hope you're ready for me.
I want you to shout like
you really mean what you say.
Because this week is not going to be
ordinary.
THERE'S A SHIFT
THAT HAS TO TAKE PLACE.
TIRED OF GETTING TIRED
OF being in the same place, nothing
happening.
You'll become a laughingstock.
A SHIFT HAS TO TAKE PLACE.
People must witness
there is a change in your life.
I want you to shout it. I step into my
divine shift now.
Come on, shout. I step into my divine
shift now.
Every stagnant area of my life
begins to move.
Every closed door
opens by fire.
I don't like the way you're saying it.
I don't like the way you're saying it. I
really want you to say it until the
devil runs away. CAN YOU SAY EVERY
CLOSED DOOR?
OPENS BY FIRE.
EVERY CLOSED DOOR
CAN YOU SEE THE DOORS AS YOU SAY THAT?
OPENS BY FIRE.
I BREAK OUT OF EVERY OLD CYCLE.
I ENTER INTO NEW LEVELS OF FAVOR.
AGAIN, I ENTER INTO NEW LEVELS OF FAVOR.
LEVELS OF GRACE.
And speed.
NO MORE DELAY.
IN JESUS' NAME.
MY SEASON HAS CHANGED.
FOR GOOD.
BEGINNING TODAY.
IN JESUS' NAME.
AMEN.
GIVE THE LORD [screaming] A BIG CLAP
OFFERING.
HALLELUJAH.
Your season changes.
Oh, your season will change. OH, IT WILL
NOT BE BUSINESS as usual.
Look at your neighbor. Look at your
neighbor. Look at your neighbor good.
BECAUSE THE NEXT TIME YOU SEE THEM, YOU
WILL NOT recognize them. LOOK AT YOUR
NEIGHBOR. LOOK AT YOUR NEIGHBOR GOOD.
BECAUSE THE NEXT TIME YOU SEE THEM,
YOU'LL WONDER IF THEY ARE THE ONES.
HALLELUJAH. THE SHIFT IS TAKING PLACE.
THE SHIFT IS TAKING PLACE. THE SHIFT IS
TAKING PLACE. TO GOD BE THE GLORY.
HALLELUJAH.
I want to declare.
Your shift will confuse your enemies.
Oh, can you say a better amen?
YOUR SHIFT WILL CONFUSE YOUR ENEMIES.
I feel it in MY SPIRIT. YOUR SHIFT WILL
CONFUSE YOUR ENEMIES.
That is the word God has given me for
you.
Your shift will confuse your enemies.
Your shift will confirm God's word.
And your shift will catapult you
into your purpose
in Jesus' name.
Shout a big amen.
SHOUT A THUNDEROUS AMEN.
LOOK AT FIVE PEOPLE, SHAKE THEIR HANDS,
AND TELL THEM I'M SHIFTING. I'M
SHIFTING. I'm shifting. Come on. Just
declare I'm shifting. I'm shifting. I'm
shifting. I am shifting. I'm shifting.
I'm shifting. I'm shifting. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
on.
>> [music]
>> I am shifting. I'M SHIFTING. I'M
SHIFTING.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Let me tell you.
Don't
wait
for the shift.
Walk
into
the shift.
>> [music]
>> Did you hear what I just said?
A lot of you have been waiting for the
shift.
And God has been waiting
on you.
From today
from today
don't wait for the shift. Walk
into
the shift. And the church says, "Amen."
And the church says,
>> [music]
>> I didn't want to do this, but And the
church says
>> [screaming]
>> Amen.
Father, thank you for the time we're
about in your house, and thank you for
this great
shift that you're bringing.
Lives have to change.
King of glory,
HEAVEN HAS OPENED,
and heaven is waiting upon us. Bless
your people, oh God,
even during this week.
Let your hand be upon them, Lord, and
may they witness that truly God has
spoken to them and has led them and has
directed them. We magnify you, we
worship you. In Jesus' name, again
somebody say a big amen.
Somebody say a big amen.
Put your hands together for Jesus.
>> [music]
>> Hallelujah.
Hallelujah.